You can eat until you are full. You are welcome to drink as much as
you want
. Thank you, auntie.
My classmates were really shocked
by how much food there is.
I estimate that
it would take three or four people to eat everything in this area
. Everyone likes to pick up the bargains.
There are so many people. Everyone is here.
Take them out one by one.
Everyone is rushing to
grab a pair of shoes.
I don’t know which athlete wears
them so well. Brothers,
coucou les amis (French: Hello, friends)
Hello, all the cuties of Shitu.
I am your Yooupi,
welcome to my channel.
In the last issue, I went to the China House to have a meal and
the comment section started to say:
If you have the ability, you can go to the Olympic Village and have a meal.
If you have the ability, you can go to the Olympic Village to pick up trash.
I am the person
But everyone knows that
the security level of the Olympic Village is very, very, very high.
It is very, very, very difficult to enter the Olympic Village.
But today I got a very precious opportunity.
A very heavyweight wanted to take me
. Entering the Olympic Village,
Aunt Ni.
Hello, Yooupi audience.
I am Aunt Ni. Welcome to the Olympic Village.
Thank you, Aunt Ni.
Aunt Ni is great.
This is the last train to catch you.
Yes
, and I have never been in,
so I feel like I don’t care. It's very strict
, not just anyone can go in
. We are the key protection targets.
They are all pandas.
They are all pandas
. And I saw that many athletes are preparing to leave today.
There are already a lot of people leaving one after another.
But today is the big team,
Yooupi, you. When I was in the Air Force, I took this to the cafeteria
to eat until I was full. You can drink whatever you want. Don't be
polite
. Thank you , Aunt
Ni . Aunt Ni already knows about it. Can you
tell me to go in? If you are in the Air Force, remember to take it to eat.
That's great.
Bye, Aunt Ni. Thank you,
Ni. My aunt left her name on the table tennis racket.
I am so happy.
I really want to take it back and treasure it.
I have now got my admission ticket.
The entire Olympic Village is built on the Seine River.
The scenery is very beautiful.
This Olympic Games The village is really big. Come and see,
there are athletes from all over the world living here.
It’s almost a country. Almost one building.
This is our China building.
Come on, China and the giant panda
athletes are leaving.
These are all athletes
from Canada. There are really trash cans here in
Athletes.
You can see that their trash cans are sorted.
This is food waste
, and the plastic and aluminum on top are
recyclable garbage.
It's not easy to pick up.
There are plastic bottles
, but plastic bottles in France cannot be exchanged for money.
It is different from Germany. Different
here, there are many kinds of stools, benches and so on.
I don’t know if I need these.
These should all be required.
This athlete brother gave me a bottle of water.
Welcome
. Thank you.
You’re welcome.
Hello .
Say hello in Chinese. Hello , you
shouldn’t say you’re welcome,
you’re welcome, you
’re welcome.
This guy also met a lot of Chinese spectators
during the Olympics.
He said that he was free to buy that drink,
and then he just bought it and asked me what I wanted to drink.
I said drink water,
what do you want? Don't talk
nonsense. There are a lot of trash cans
. Without further ado, I'm going to take a look and see
if there
's
anything
there. Let's talk about
the cardboard box.
What's this? You see, there are hangers and boxes
like this in this trash can. This
is a French rooster, but there are no shoes in it. It would be ok
if I could pick up a pair of shoes.
What is this? This is
a fun
fan from the French team.
You can take it away
and take a look at it.
It’s all wrapped up. Can you open it
?
It’s ridiculous. It
’s so sunny today in France. The temperature is 38 degrees.
I am walking through the entire Olympic Village right now.
You can take a look
around and see the dormitories where athletes live.
The greening in the Olympic Village is actually quite good
in various countries.
The buildings above where athletes live
will be reused
and will not be demolished. It's a nice
place to take pictures and you're really not afraid of falling down.
Those are Australian athletes here.
Take a photo as a souvenir.
Today is the last day of the Olympic Games.
Most of the athletes have to leave.
We are here today to help the athletes transport their luggage.
This is an event. It was an unforgettable Olympics.
I went to watch various competitions
and saw athletes from all over the world.
The atmosphere was very lively
and very shocking.
I saw this situation and it was very difficult to pick up garbage.
Let’s see. If not, I would go to
this cafeteria to work. The entrance is very impressive.
On both sides are the national flags of various countries.
Let
's go in and take a look.
The entire cafeteria is very large
and should be able to accommodate.
I think there are at least tens of thousands of people eating there,
all of them athletes from various countries.
He made the entire cafeteria into a It feels like a train
, and the garbage classification is also done very well.
Below are the classification bins for various garbage.
Now let's take a plate and open it directly.
Now all you can see is the salad area.
It is said that this time the salad counter alone
has hundreds of choices
. I have to save my stomach for dinner
at one o'clock . It's
so rich.
There's also a big slice of meat here.
Is this ham?
A whole slice of
various French cheeses.
This one is soft,
and then there's this hard cheese.
Okay. I've already I got my appetizer.
Just now you have also seen that
there are really many types of it.
This is just the variety of appetizers.
They taste very light and
refreshing.
I think it must be specially prepared
for athletes. After
we finish eating, You can enter the staple food area.
The super popular chocolate muffins
are all here. Get one here. Oh my god,
hurry up and get one
. This one is very popular on the Internet.
You must try one.
There are all kinds of cold yogurt and
cheese.
In front of it is the fruit area. There is
a whole bowl and a whole bowl of
honey.
I have watermelon .
I want some pineapple.
I also want a blueberry.
There are also various jams
and some yogurt. I think it’s okay.
There are also various cookies
and there is
too much
bread. I have already taken so much in one circle.
In front of it is the staple food counter.
There are noodles
and grilled food
here , and there are also daily dishes.
I want a chicken, a fish, and
some other vegetables
. There are so many leaves.
The students were really shocked
that there were so many foods inside.
If you want to eat them all,
I estimate that
it would take three or four people to finish the food in this area.
There are also various drinks
here. Oranges juice
And there is this kind of drink that comes out right here
and water.
Let’s get a frozen orange juice. Wow
, is Zhang Mingyu
Yooupi? Yes, it’s
such an honor that
she actually knows me
. Really,
which of my videos do you like?
I personally like it better.
You have collaborated with some other UP masters on some videos,
right?
Yes
, I thought it might be interesting,
so
the interactive atmosphere would be better.
Then I recently watched your latest video.
Did you catch a crab? or did you catch it? What
I am still paying more attention to
is actually I want to take a test
to see if you are a true fan of mine.
If you are really a true fan of mine,
the issue of catching crayfish in the Seine River
is
correct. I also want to ask about
it. Is it very difficult for us to enter the canteen of the Olympic Village?
Generally speaking, only athletes can enter.
Others need to apply
and obtain meal tickets before they can enter the canteen.
I wish you all the best on your return to China.
I also watched your competition. It 's very exciting.
Thank you
for the shooting. The photo was also very good.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Well, for the first round of
meat, I ordered a piece of chicken, a piece of fish,
and a chicken drumstick here
. Then I drank fruit
, yogurt,
and chocolate muffin cake.
It was so delicious. Now let
’s try the fish
pan-fried salmon.
The salad just now and the dish I’m eating now
feel relatively light in taste.
It doesn’t feel particularly heavy with oil and salt
, but it feels very healthy.
It’s worthy of being eaten by athletes.
Let’s take a look at the environment.
Now you can sit here outside the shed, and you can also sit
here. This is the dining area.
We queued all the way over there,
and then received the meal all the way.
I tried the chicken legs again.
The chicken legs were quite thin.
I saw that I used to run a lot of chicken before I was alive.
He added sweet and sour. Barbecue sauce
is still suitable for me to eat this kind of salty and flavorful thing
, but to be honest, it's very hot.
There are only a few fans in this shed. It's
really sweaty to eat here
. For the second round, let's start.
There's pizza here,
this pizza. There is so much cheese, it must be delicious.
There are also all kinds of cereals here.
I really can’t eat anymore.
This is soy milk, this is oat milk
, this is almond milk. I drink this.
In fact, there are quite a lot of things in it,
and it tastes good,
but I can’t help it. My belly is too small
and I can’t waste it
. Let’s take as much as we can.
We’re almost done.
Finally, I’d like to share with you the chocolate muffin.
Athletes from all over the world came to grab it.
It was gone when I went over to look at
it. The whole cake was special.
Isn’t it delicious when you eat it and then eat it
with the flow of chocolate
? After eating, I came out to see
how wide the place is. The place
I just ate in
is still the same place.
I think there is nothing wrong with it except for the hot spot. It
’s pretty good. It’s delicious
and there are so many dishes.
If you’re not full when you’re walking,
there are all kinds of fruits at the door. You can grab
apricots, peaches, and bananas.
What are you looking for ?
Can I get it for free?
Isn’t this great?
There are so many things that
I can get for free .
There are so many days.
Thank you.
Take whatever
you want. God, I also want to go in and get
something. There is bread, milk,
and bread.
Many people are taking it.
Look at
this athlete. There are so many Cokes. Do
you
want a can?
Thank you.
Is it Coke?
Is it orange flavored ?
Coke is about the same
as Fanta. Orange soda
is awesome. There
are all kinds of food.
This is a Korean counter.
These are all Korean food.
Is this rice?
Yes, rice
is edible.
So many people are grabbing my heavenly
milk.
There's still a lot of milk
. If I don't take it, there's no
soy sauce.
I don't know what
string beans are .
Okay
, I'm joining the army.
Take it.
Everyone takes it. I take it
too. What kind of coffee is this?
I don't care. Take it first
. Shoes
, hurry up. Let me grab a pair
. Let me get a pair. Get a pair
. I grabbed a pair
of shoes .
I don’t know which athlete wore them. They are
so awesome. Brothers, it’s
size 47. I’ll
just change them. It
fits
perfectly
. It’s cool.
There
are also two water bottles.
This guy picked them up. Here
is milk.
What kind of milk powder is this?
Milk powder seems to be taken in a pack.
What are these things?
No matter if it is taken away
, there are small bottles of milk.
Take these two bottles away
. Everyone likes to pick up cheap ones.
Many people came to
this one. Take them out one by one and
everyone is grabbing
tablecloths
. But
the logistics department takes out box after box for
everyone to
take and that's it
. There are all kinds of things. The kettle is
in
good condition.
I picked up a set of
kettles for boiling
hot water. It's
very new
, yes, it's very good.
Everyone is picking up here.
Are there any mirrors? Have you picked up all of them?
There is also a mirror
that is awesome.
Look at the various types of mirrors that
this old lady picked up.
Which country's athletes picked them up?
What kind
of bandages are these
? There are so many bandages
. I have already picked them up.
Many of the things they grabbed are in front.
I came here late.
There is a table.
If you want to take it, you can take it.
I don’t want this table.
I really want to take it
, but just I can't move it alone
. It would be great if there was someone
. It's completely usable when I take it back.
I came late and didn't grab anything
, but I got a pair of shoes. There were only 4 pairs.
I grabbed a pair. I definitely couldn't wear them,
but I can get them. Go give it to someone
, and you can grab these drinks and other things.
These shoes are completely good.
The whole shoe is okay.
Although I didn’t pick up many myself
, people around me picked up a lot.
They use a trailer to tow them
all and take them away with
the cart. Push them directly to
you. When he finished,
he took out all these and gave them to the athletes
, and the athletes took them away directly
, which means that nothing was wasted.
Moreover, this year's Olympics also has an environmental theme
, such as the uneasy air conditioner that we have been complaining about.
It's an environmentally friendly concept.
Now I'm out and
looking at my clothes.
I've been walking in them
all day and I'm covered in sweat. Don't blame me. Look,
my back must be covered in sweat stains.
It's too hot. The weather is like today
and I'm
taking the photo alone. The teacher is waiting outside for me
to show you my results today.
Photographer: Wow, these are all picked up by you.
And the shoes
are said to be worn by which athlete.
I didn’t hear clearly. A bunch of people grabbed them.
Then there is something to drink here.
I picked up a lot
, so please give me a thumbs up for such exciting content.
You see, I have worked so hard
and it’s been a bumper day.
I’ve been eating and taking things.
I’m really exhausted today.
So let’s do the next one.
Goodbye video